Privacy Policy
==============

**SPN Privacy Policy**  
In this policy “SPN” refers to SPN staff, board members, and contractors, all of whom are bound by law or contract to keep information they receive as part of their work with SPN confidential.

As to all of the information described below, SPN will not give, sell, rent or exchange the information with anyone else without your prior consent except as compelled by law (see the final section).

**Website Privacy Policy**  
SPN servers may record the numerical Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

We use this information to measure the number of visitors to different sections of the site, to diagnose and correct system errors, and to improve the site.

We do not connect this information to your name or identity.

We do not use “cookies” on this site unless, as a member, you access the “Members Only” sections of the website.

**Membership and Contributions Privacy Policy**  
SPN will never share or use your personal information for any reason other than to manage your membership or contribution.

Credit card information will be used only for the specified use, and is not retained once the specified transaction is completed. Credit card information is managed and processed via a secure third-party source, [Verisign.](http://www.verisign.com/)

Personal and contact information provided as part of our membership application or as a donation will be used only for the purpose specified, and will not be sold, disclosed, or otherwise revealed to third parties.

**Compelled Disclosure**  
If we are required by law to disclose the information that you have submitted, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made in order to give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure. We will attempt to provide this notice by email, if you have given us an email address, or by postal mail if you have entered a postal address. We will independently object to overly broad requests for access to information about users of our site. If you do not challenge the disclosure request, we may be legally required to turn over your information.

If you have any additional questions about our privacy policy at this time, please [email us](mailto:patrick@spn.org).

This privacy policy is derived in part with permission from the privacy policy of the [Electronic Frontier Foundation](http://www.eff.org/).
